You are what you eat.
Venom: Let There Be Carnage is a science fiction, action,
adventure film directed by Andy Serkis.
After finding a host body in investigative reporter Eddie Brock, the alien symbiote must
face a new enemy, Carnage, the alter ego of serial killer Cletus Kasady.
Eddie Brock / Venom, played by Tom Hardy.
Cletus Kasady / Carnage, played by Woody Harrelson.
Anne Weying, played by Michelle Williams.
Frances Louise Barrison / Shriek, played by Naomie Harris.
Dr. Dan Lewis, played by Reid Scott.
Detective Mulligan, played by Stephen Graham.
Venom: Let There Be Carnage is a 2021 American superhero film
based on the Marvel Comics character Venom.
The sequel to Venom (2018) and the second film in Sony's Spider-Man Universe (SSU),
it was directed by Andy Serkis from a screenplay by Kelly Marcel.
Tom Hardy stars as Eddie Brock and Venom alongside Michelle Williams,
Naomie Harris, Reid Scott, Stephen Graham, and Woody Harrelson.
In the film, Eddie and the alien symbiote Venom must face serial killer Cletus Kasady
(Harrelson) after he becomes the host of an offshoot of Venom named Carnage.
Venom was intended by Sony Pictures to be the start of a new shared universe,
and plans for a sequel began during production on the first film.
Harrelson was cast to make a brief appearance as Cletus at the end of Venom, with
the intention of him becoming the villain Carnage in the sequel.
Official work on the sequel began in January 2019, with Hardy and
Harrelson confirmed to return along with Marcel as writer.
Serkis was hired as director that August, partly due to his experience working with computer-generated imagery (CGI)
and motion capture technology, which was an important part of portraying Venom and Carnage in the film.
Filming took place at Leavesden Studios in England from November 2019 to
February 2020, with additional filming in San Francisco in February.
The title was announced in April 2020.
Marco Beltrami was hired to compose the film's score,
replacing Ludwig Göransson from the previous film.
Venom: Let There Be Carnage premiered in London on September 14, 2021, and was theatrically released in the United
States on October 1, after multiple delays from an initial October 2020 date due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
The film received mixed reviews from critics but was a box office success, grossing $506
million worldwide and becoming the seventh-highest-grossing film of 2021.
A sequel, Venom: The Last Dance, was released on October 25, 2024.
The film explores themes of hero, psychopath, superhero, anti hero, villain.
The tone is thought_provoking.